<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Musthofa Syarifudin</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Musthofa Syarifudin</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 10:23:51 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 10:23:51 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 class=&#34;heading&#34; id=&#34;musthofa-syarifudin&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Musthofa Syarifudin&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;anchor&#34; href=&#34;#musthofa-syarifudin&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud/Infra Software Engineer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:thofaden@email.com&#34;&gt;Email&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/musthofa-s-bb3616179&#34;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/mtfsy&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;heading&#34; id=&#34;-summary&#34;&gt;&#xA;  📄 Summary&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;anchor&#34; href=&#34;#-summary&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am a versatile and experienced Software Engineer dedicated to improving software delivery and optimization. My professional journey has taken me through the consulting, mining, and high-growth startup sectors, giving me a unique and adaptable skill set. My expertise covers the full spectrum of the development lifecycle, from designing and implementing robust CI/CD pipelines with tools like GitHub Actions and Jenkins to managing and securing diverse infrastructure across on-premises environments and major cloud platforms like AWS, Google Cloud, and Azure. I am highly proficient in establishing comprehensive observability with tools such as Datadog, Azure Monitor, and Google Cloud Logging, while also leveraging automation with Terraform and Ansible. I have extensive experience with various databases, including MySQL, PostgreSQL, and BigQuery, and I am skilled in crucial security measures like network hardening and incident response using Microsoft Sentinel. Finally, I am focused on building efficient and scalable Internal Developer Platforms using Docker and Kubernetes, with a special focus on managing these platforms on GKE and AKS.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Log-Structured Merge Tree</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/windows_bloatware_issue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/windows_bloatware_issue/</guid>
      <description>An LSM Tree overview and Java implementation.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
